Are you all right?
You can see me?
Eh?
Never mind.
Did something sad happen?
Because...
You're crying.
Oh, you're right.
You're weird.
I'm not weird.
Sorry, did I make you mad?
No, I'm happy.
I've always been alone.
So you're also alone.
You too?
Yeah, I just can't seem to make friends.
I guess we're the same.
The same?
Yeah.
Then, will you stay together with me?
Yeah. Let's be friends!
Okay.
It's all right.
It won't hurt.
I love you, Taito.
I'm alive?
What happened?
So you're the rumored Saitohimea?
Nice to meet you. I'm Hinata.
Were you sent from the Church?
Give me a break already!
I'm not with Bahlskra anymore.
I'm not going to remove his seal.
So please...
The Church? What's that?
A monster!
So that's how it is. You're just another demon worshipper.
Stop it!
Taito!
Oh?
Let Himea go!
He doesn't even die from that, huh?
Saitohimea.
What kind of power did you give him?
Like I'd tell you!
Hmm... Well, it doesn't matter.
Damn it... Damn it, damn it!
Damn it! Why can't I save her?!
Heh, I've killed him six times already and he still won't die.
Taito...
Stop it! I beg you!
Oh? So he'll stop reviving?
I guess there's a limit to the number of times he'll be able to do that.
So that would mean he won't come back to life if he dies a seventh time, wouldn't it?
You shouldn't hide stuff like that.
It will reset every fifteen minutes.
And then he can die another six times, huh?
That's how the curse I placed on Taito works.
You've fallen for him, huh?
So you foolishly granted him a power
that prevents him from dying,
just so he could stay by your side forever.
Is that true, Himea?
Please stop it.
I'll do as you say.
So please stop embarrassing me like this in front of Taito.
He'll be a nuisance,
so I'll erase his memories.
Stop!
I don't want to forget about Himea!
I... I definitely won't forget about you!
I'll definitely come and save you!
Just wait!
I will never...
forget about...
Forget about her already.
Don't go, my non-existent future
だから行かないで、僕のいない未来
dakara ikanaide, boku no inai mirai
I still haven't forgotten the feelings of that moment
あの一瞬の想いはまだ忘れない
ano isshun no omoi wa mada wasurenai
The word engraved deep in my heart ever since that day
あの日胸の奥握り締めた言葉
ano hi mune no oku nigirishimeta kotoba
That one single word changed my tomorrow
あの一言が明日を変えてくれたんだね
ano hitokoto ga ashita o kaete kuretan da ne
I'm watching a dream
僕は夢を見てる
boku wa yume o miteru
I wonder if it's my own dream
それは僕だけの夢かな
sore wa boku dake no yume kana
You're watching the sky
君は空を見てる
kimi wa sora o miteru
It's your own sky
それは君だけの空
sore wa kimi dake no sora
Once, just once
一つだけ　一つだけ
hitotsu dake hitotsu dake
As long as we hold what's important in our hearts
大切なもの胸にあれば
taisetsuna mono mune ni areba
We can get through both grief and endless nights
長い夜も嘆きも越えられるだろう
nagai yoru mo nageki mo koerareru darou
Just once, alone with you
一度だけ　君とだけ
ichido dake kimi to dake
These controversial dreams are all I have
かもした夢が僕の全て
kamoshita yume ga boku no subete
Cleared of my life, my desire to protect you remains
命を解け君を守りたい強く思う
inochi o toke kimi o mamoritai tsuyoku omou
This is the feeling I now call love
こんな気持ちを今愛と呼ぶよ
konna kimochi o ima ai to yobuyo
Hinata, damn you!
Hinata?
Don't lump me together with that worthless scum.
Kurenai Gekkou?!
Huh?
Is your back okay?
Why would you attack Himea?
Because that woman is pursued by Hinata.
I have no idea what you're talking about!
「900 seconds of afterschool 」
That's fine. Small fry like you don't need to know.
Now hand her over.
Hell no!
Fool.
You're faster than I thought, but you're no match for me.
I see.
So that's the kind of power a Vampire's pitiful Sacrifice receives.
Gekkou!
I got your cola!
You're late!
But, um... You see... There was this head rolling around, then it went like "GASSHIN" and reattached!
It was crazy!
It's him! Immortal-kun!
They're our enemies.
Mirai, go and kill them already.
Enemies?
They're all worn out...
Doesn't that kind of make us look like the bad guys here?
Well, you're always the bad guy, but...
You're wrong.
I'm a genius.
That's right, a genius bad guy.
Silence. Do as I tell you to.
You belong to me, remember?
B-Belong to...
O-Okay.
The curse is gone!
Mirai of Andu is now fully functional!
S-Seriously?
You're that Andou Mirai?
Shocky Shock attack!
Taito!
Here's another Shocky Shock!
Aruto!
The heck's this, it's awesome!
Whoa, Gekkou! I can't move!
You useless small fry.
Now the tides have turned.
What will you do?
For now, just drop your sword.
Or something might happen to the hostage.
Release Mirai.
Really?! No way!
Gekkou did that for me!
Silence, you hindrance.
It's not for your sake.
I just don't need this sword to take care of this trash.
You can just die.
Telling her to die?
I'm suddenly in a really good mood now.
So maybe I should get a little serious.
What is she?
Roar!
I'm a monster!
Taito!
Hey, how far am I going to fly?!
There you are.
Those are some serious jumping skills.
Aww, can't you compliment me in some other way?
If that's the best you've got after all this time, you can't be popular with the girls.
Actually, I'm not.
So you're not?
But to me you're popular, so it's okay.
I love you, Taito.
I'll give you something nice.
Something nice?
Yes. Something nice.
It's hot!
Of course it is.
It's a forbidden spell that even we Vampires can't use.
The moment one uses it, it will consume the whole upper body.
Then what if a human like me used it?
I see. If it's my body...
That's right.
Use it to defeat him.
And there you have it!
If you give up now, I'll forgive you!
You wish.
I thought you'd say that!
Exorcise, Spell Error!
Just give up already!
Aren't you in high spirits for a small fry?
Taito!
Gekkou!
I'll help you, Taito!
I'll help Gekkou!
No need to!
Then how about I get rid of you all at once?
Taito!
Gekkou!
A spider?!
And it is huge!
Over there!
Huh? There are two Gekkous?
N-No, Taito...
He came after me again.
It's Hinata.
He's the one who...
Stay out of it.
I'm going to kill him.
Bullshit!  He's-
Shut up, trash!
My failure of a little twin brother
will be my prey!
Little brother?!
I wonder who the real failure is, Nii-san.
I see you're using my second-hand goods.
S-Second-hand goods?!
Shut up, Mirai!
I'll return the humiliation he put you through.
Gekkou!
Can you take care of that monster?
Y-Yeah! I can!
I'm so taking care of it!
I see. I'll leave this to you,
since you can take care of it after all.
Wait!
I'm going!
W-We should take this chance to run away, Taito!
We can't win against him!
He's too strong!
Say, Himea.
I know I kept you waiting for those nine years and all,
but could you just wait another five minutes?
Huh?
I'll beat the crap out of him and be right back with you.
Taito.
Okay. I'll fight by your side.
You don't have to force yourself.
Don't be stupid.
You can't win alone, Taito.
Really?
Yes. But we might have a chance if we work together.
Over these nine years, you've grown so strong and cool...
Yeah.
I could have gone on with my normal life, since I'd forgrotten all about Himea.
But, I didn't do nothing all the time.
I was quite good at karate.
I'm sure that was all for Himea's sake.
So that I could protect her the next time we would meet.
Shocky Shock attack!
Oh, it seems like you did improve a little.
Yeah, just a little.
Just a little effort and I was suddenly a million steps ahead of you.
It's over, Hinata.
A million steps?
You mean a million steps behind me, don't you?
You shouldn't be so easily impressed by your meager power.
Out of the way, idiot!
A million steps ahead and yet you need four people to fight.
As expected of you, Nii-san.
Hey, Kurogane Taito.
What?
Help me out here.
Oh? You finally decided to be honest with yourself?
Yeah.
But I'm not about to let someone who made fun of me get away.
So, do you have a plan?
Can you do that again?
Then you go and get him. And then...
You're already out of options.
Let's put an end to this.
Do I kill everyone except Saitohimea?
Or would you rather hand her over to save your own lives?
We decline both options!
I'll beat the crap out of you and protect Himea!
Is that so?
Go!
Taito!
I did it...
That power is quite troublesome.
Did you get that from her?
That's unfair.
After all the torture I've put you through, you never gave me anything.
Anyway, you seem to be the biggest for now.
Six times...
So the next time is the last.
It's just like nine years ago, huh?
You haven't progressed at all.
Stop it already!
Sure, if you want it that way.
But this time you'll properly promise
to become my slave.
I'll be your slave or whatever else you want!
Just don't hurt...
Taito...
Gekkou!
Don't do it, Himea.
You can't become his slave.
It's okay. I'll protect you this time.
Just wait there.
I'll beat the crap out of him and return to your side.
You'll protect her?
In this situation?
Hey, monster!
Don't!
Everything will be over if you die now.
Himea gave me my life.
So if it will save her...
And make up for these nine years...
If it can make her live with a smile on her face...
I'll give you my life!
Kurogane!
Fool.
You don't stand a chance.
Of course I do, idiot.
I already decided...
that I won't forget Himea again!
No!
You did well, for a small fry.
Like you're one to talk.
Taito...
Taito!
Oh, sorry...
Seems like I made you cry again.
Morning!
Hey, wake up!
Huh? I'm alive?
Still dozing?
Oh? Who's that?
They say it's a transfer student.
Hi-Himea?!
Taito!
I missed you!
Ouch!
I-It wasn't a dream?
T-Then why am I...?
I missed you.
I missed you so much.
No way!
T-Taito?
Kurenai Gekkou?
Student Council
From today on, you're my slaves.
I'll have you working in my student council.
Who are you calling a slave?!
You're a trashy slave.
Or what did you think?
Want me to beat it into your thick head?
Oh, try me.
We'll settle yesterday's...
Hey Himea, could you let go already?
Nope.
Nope?
I'll be together with you forever, Taito!
I'm looking forward to it!
Himea...
That's all. Get lost.
Don't go deciding things on your own!
I have no intention of serving you!
This was the beginning of everything.
The beginning of this bothersome story of how our worlds connected.
Quietly quivering to the end of my memories
tsuioku no hate ni shizuka ni yurameku
追憶の果てに静かに揺らめく
An everlasting, distant promise
eien ni tsuzuku haruka no yakusoku
永遠に続く遥かの約束
Break the cicada, drowned in sorrow
kanashimi ni noreta utsusemi kowashite
悲しみに濡れた空蝉壊して
My despair was replaced, but the loneliness was standing out
zetsubou o surikaete kodoku wa medatteta
絶望をすり替えて孤独は目立ってた
I was on my own, until the day I met with you
tada hitori kimi ni deau hi made
ただひとり君に出会う日まで
Come here, let's put our hearts together
koko e oide kokoro kasaneyou
ここへおいで　心重ねよう
I'll remove your thorns for you
kimi no toge o torisatte ageru
君の棘を取り去ってあげる
Play to our crumbled future
kuzure ochita mirai e kanaderu
崩れ落ちた未来へ奏でる
Scream out louder and then let us kiss
sakebigoe o hiroi agete kuchizuke kawasou
叫び声を拾い上げて口付け交わそう
Come here, let's put our hearts together
koko e oide kokoro kasaneyou
ここへおいで　心重ねよう
Play to our crumbled future
kuzure ochita mirai e kanaderu
崩れ落ちた未来へ奏でる
I got killed out of nowhere, and then I'm suddenly alive again.
Then this incredibly beautiful girl says she loves me.
And then I'm treated like a slave by that arrogant student council president.
What the hell happened to my high school life?!
Well, at least I won't be bored, I guess.
After all, Himea's cute, soft and she's got a nice scent...
The heck?!
Is this how I'm going to live for the next three years?!
Oh, yeah. I've already died once.
Next time  「The <> sways by the poolside」
But that's hardly the problem here!